We all hear about foreign actors making it big in Hollywood.
我们都听说过外国演员在好莱坞大获成功的故事。
But many acknowledge that they were shaking in their boots the first time they were waiting for the director to shout: 'Action!'
但许多人承认，当他们第一次等待导演喊“开拍”时，他们紧张得发抖。
Spanish actress Penelope Cruz, star of Zoolander 2 and Vanilla Sky, is a respected actress with a Hollywood career.
西班牙女演员佩内洛普·克鲁兹是《超级名模2》和《香草天空》中的明星，是一位备受尊敬的拥有好莱坞职业生涯的女演员。
But she hardly spoke any English when she was cast in her first role in an English language movie in 1998.
但她在1998年首次出演英语电影时几乎不会说英语。
In a candid interview with the US broadcaster CBS, Penelope admitted: "I would lock myself in the bathroom and cry because I didn't understand what was going on on the set, because I didn't understand everything that the director was saying or what the other actors were saying."
在一次接受美国广播公司CBS的采访时，佩内洛普坦承：“我会把自己锁在浴室里哭，因为我不明白片场发生了什么，因为我不明白导演在说什么，也不明白其他演员在说什么。”
Closer to home we have the example of Ziyi Zhang.
我们更熟悉的例子是章子怡。
She gained international acclaim in Memoirs of a Geisha and Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon and received many nominations for awards.
她因《艺伎回忆录》和《卧虎藏龙》获得国际赞誉，并多次获得奖项提名。
What's helped her to learn English?
是什么帮助她学习英语的呢？
Well, she says she listened to Eminem songs.
她说她听埃米纳姆的歌。
And as she learned the language, she realised "how rude" the lyrics were.
当她掌握了这门语言，她才意识到歌词是“多么粗俗”。
But when it comes to acting in English, nobody has a more colourful story than Austrian Arnold Schwarzenegger.
但一谈到用英语表演，没有人比奥地利人阿诺德·施瓦辛格的故事更丰富多彩了。
He had to be dubbed at the beginning of his career because nobody could make out what he was saying.
在他职业生涯的初期，他不得不被配音，因为没有人能理解他在说什么。
In his next film, he played a deaf mute.
在他的下一部电影中，他扮演了一个聋哑人。
Yes - the complicated name, the thick accent, the big body - nothing stopped him from doing the things he liked.
是的——复杂的名字、浓重的口音、庞大的身躯——没有什么能阻止他做自己喜欢的事情。
So don't despair when you struggle with English.
所以，当你在英语学习中遇到挫折时，不要绝望。
They've all been there and they've prevailed.
他们都经历过，并且成功了。
Are you ready for your close up in life?
你准备好迎接你生命中的特写镜头了吗？